mytweeple.com 2014-06-25

# Contaxio | Relationship Management | Contact Management - Privacy Policy

###  Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is effective as of March 14, 2014. This Policy may be amended from time to time; notices of amendments will appear at the bottom of this Policy. It is your responsibility to review this Policy and to check for notices of amendments.

**Personal Information**

We collect account information from social sites such as Twitter, LinkedIn, and Facebook when you apply to become a Registered User of the Contaxio website (the “Site) and when you use the Contaxio software program (the “Program”). You may also opt to provide us with your e-mail address as part of your Contaxio settings.  We use the personal information you share with us to ensure the content and services that we provide are tailored to your current and future needs. We may use it to solicit feedback and respond to that feedback. We may use it to alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information, and new services. Within 10 days of your request, we will refrain from sending email to you. We do not share this personal information with third parties, except as otherwise permissible by law.

**Cookies**

The Site and the Program require cookies to function. Cookies are used to ensure the correct functioning of the service we provide. We use cookies only for this purpose. If you disable cookies in your browser you will be unable to use the Site or the Program. We are not responsible for any cookies on the Site used by other service providers.

**Server Logs**

Our web server and parts of the Site log your usage activity. We use logs to provide site-wide reporting, to ensure smooth operation of the services, and for general web site and application maintenance. Like almost all Internet servers, logged information may include timestamps, your client IP address (as it appears to the server), and the page(s) you visit. We will not share our detailed server logs with any third party. We may however elect to publish aggregate statistics on visitor activity from time to time based on log information (e.g. "we had 1,234 visitors yesterday"). We will not publish any personally identifiable information in these publications.

**Links**

For your convenience, we may offer links to other websites. Please note this Privacy Policy applies only to this Site. Any other website may be subject to another privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy posted at each website you visit before you provide any personal information through that website.

**Notice on Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

While we take seriously the privacy of all our visitors, we are especially committed to protecting the privacy of children under the age of 13 years old. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. Any personal information that is unknowingly collected from a child under the age of 13 years old will be deleted upon written request from the child’s parent or legal guardian. Deletion requests should be sent to support [at] contax.io

If you have any questions about Contaxio privacy policies please contact support [at] contax.io.

Date of last amendment: March 14, 2014
